// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q011: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Mr. Schaeffer managed to finish his new novel even though ------ had only a few days until the deadline.',
      choices: ['his', 'him', 'himself', 'he'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['he'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'First West Bank offers low------interest mortgages online to customers ------ the country.',
      choices: ['throughout', 'among', 'during', 'onto'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['throughout'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Toyo Media Group has 15 branches in Asia, three of ------ are in Japan.',
      choices: ['those', 'these', 'them', 'which'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['which'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: '------ your purchase has not arrived on the scheduled delivery date, please contact us using the form on our website.',
      choices: ['In case of', 'Unless', 'In the event that', 'As'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['that'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'If you receive a refund, you must show ------ of purchase, such as a receipt.',
      choices: ['proof', 'preference', 'profile', 'revenue'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['proof'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Siesna Construction worked ------ with Gessen Design Office on a project to install solar panels on the roof of City Hall.',
      choices: ['hardly', 'prominently', 'approximately', 'closely'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['closely'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Machines purchased from us come with a free one------year repair ------ from the date of purchase.',
      choices: ['excerpt', 'warranty', 'invitation', 'connection'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['warranty'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Trattoria Gennaro has expanded its lunch menu and started a delivery service ------ increase sales.',
      choices: ['now that', 'in order to', 'purposely', 'rather'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['to'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: '------ the road repair work is completed, the traffic restrictions on Maple Street will be removed.',
      choices: ['Consequently', 'Once', 'Beforehand', 'Among'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Once'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Mr. Nigelâ€™s proposed promotional plan seemed quite difficult, but he was able to accomplish it ------.',
      choices: ['his', 'him', 'himself', 'he'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['himself'],
      score: 1,
    },
  ],
}